<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Northeast Geobiology Symposium 2022</title>
    <link>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Northeast Geobiology Symposium 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Code of Conduct</title>
      <link>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/conduct/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:52:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/conduct/</guid>
      <description>Code of Conduct The Northeast Geobiology Symposium should be a place where all members of our community feel safe and included. As organizers, we hope to foster a collaborative, welcoming, and respectful environment. Behavior that prevents this from happening will not be tolerated.
Audio and video recording, or taking images of a presentation without the presenters’ permission, is expressly forbidden. Images of posters taken without permission are not allowed. Images of posters may be taken with the explicit consent of the presenter, and images may be acquired only in the presence of the presenter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:52:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/contact/</guid>
      <description>Questions, comments or concerns? Email the organizing committee!
  8,000-year old capelin concretion from Kangerlussuaq, Greenland. Photo: Angel Mojarro
   Accessibility  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Covid Policies</title>
      <link>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:52:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/covid/</guid>
      <description>MIT Covid Policies We are following all of MIT&#39;s policies regarding COVID-19. In order to attend this conference, you must be fully vaccinated against COVID-19, including a booster shot. Masks are no longer required indoors at MIT.
Additional considerations We are planning a one-day NE Geobio Symposium this year in order to give folks the option of driving to and from Cambridge in the same day, avoiding an overnight stay. Weather permitting, we will have food and drinks available outdoors, while poster sessions and talks will occur in a large indoor space.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Program</title>
      <link>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/program/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:52:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/program/</guid>
      <description>Program We have an exciting lineup of early career speakers and presenters organized into three sessions of four talks each and two poster sessions of 18-20 posters each. Check them out here, or click on the logo below.
  Logo by Ellen Lalk
  --   *Logo by Ellen Lalk*
  --  Accessibility  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration</title>
      <link>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/registration/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:52:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/registration/</guid>
      <description>Registration Registration is now closed. See you on April 16! In order to attend NE Geobio (or any event at MIT), you must be fully vaccinated against COVID-19, including a booster shot.
We are hosting a one-day, in-person event at MIT. Talks and posters will be indoors in a large space; social events that include food (breakfast, coffee breaks, dinner) will be outdoors, weather permitting.
  Plan view of stromatolites in the Trezona Formation, Australia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schedule and Parking</title>
      <link>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jan 2022 11:52:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://juliawilcots.github.io/NEGeobio-2022-MIT/schedule/</guid>
      <description>Schedule We will spend the day in and around the Ray and Maria Stata Center (Building 32), located at 32 Vassar St, Cambridge MA 02139.
We are closely monitoring the local COVID situation and MIT&#39;s policies for events. The latest information can be found here.
A PDF version of the schedule is available here.
   Time Event Location     7:00 AM Earliest arrival time to park in the Stata Center lot    8:00 AM – 9:00 AM Arrival &amp;amp; Breakfast Vest Student Streets   9:00 AM - 9:10 AM Welcome &amp;amp; Land Acknowledgement 32-123   9:10 AM - 10:20 AM Session 1: Evolution, Phylogeny, and Omics 32-123   10:20 AM - 10:50 AM Coffee Break Vest Student Streets   10:50 AM - 12:00 AM Session 2: The Fossil Record &amp;amp; Diagenetic Processes 32-123   12:00 AM - 12:45 PM Lunch Forbes cafe/outside   1:00 PM - 2:30 PM Poster Session 1 Vest Student Streets   2:30 PM - 3:40 PM Session 3: Isotopes and Friends 32-123   3:40 PM - 4:00 PM Coffee and snack break Vest Student Streets   4:00 PM - 5:30 PM Poster Session 2 Vest Student Streets   5:30 PM - 7:30 PM Dinner Reception Forbes cafe/outside   8:00 PM Latest departure time from Stata Center lot     Parking Free parking is available for Symposium attendees in the Stata Center lot (Building 32) (32 Vassar St, Cambridge MA 02139).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
